Guide to the Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
- Box 35, Folder (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: Chrysler Corporation Courses in Industrial Education, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: CIO Now Demands Right to Sit on Both Sides of Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 23: What Editors Say about the Chrysler "Slow Dow" Strike, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 24: A Job with a Future, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 25: CIO-UAW and IO Foremen's Union Work Together, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 26: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation for its Airtemp Division and the International Union and Local Number 753, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 27: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and the International Association of Machinists Die Sinkers Local 1222, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 28: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and the International Union, United Automobile Workers of America, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 29: Confidential Registration for Employment, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 30: Agreement Between Chrysler Motors Parts Corporation and International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 31: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and International Union UAW of A. CIO. Local Union No. 705, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 32: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and United Sutomobile Workers of America, Local Union Numbers 7, 3, 140, 227, 490, 51, 375, 230, 371, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 33: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and the International Union, United Automobile Workers of America, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 34: Newsleter to the Employees of Chrysler Corporation, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 35: Chrysler Corporation's "Tomorrow Department", Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 36: Life of an American Workman, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 37: Management Fundamentals - Chrysler Corporation, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 38: Group Leadership. Text for Special Short Lecture Course fpr Group Leaders, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 39: Hospital and Surgical Care Plan, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 40: Employees' Savings and Investment Plan of Chrysler Corporation and its Subsidiary Companies, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 41: Chrysler Corporation Safety Rules, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 42: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation Canada Limited and Local 195 of the International Union, United Automobile Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 43: General Information for Employees, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 44: General Information for Employees, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 45: General Information for Employees, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 46: A Plan for Chrysler Corporation Employees who Desire to Purchase US Government Defense Savings Bonds, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 47: Employee Information on Ability, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 48: A Streamlined Apprentice-Training Program, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 49: Bullets by the Billion, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 50: Chrysler Corporation Safety Rules, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 51: National Apprentice Agreement, Standards and Scheduled Work Process, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 52: Agreement between International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 53: Managing Men and Preventing Misunderstanding, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 54: Five Abilities Required on any Job, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 55: Agreement Between International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 56: Agreement Between International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 57: Big Figures Don's Mean Fat Profits, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 58: Some Facts About Chrysler Corporation Before and During the War, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
    By B. E Hutchinson. Item is in English.
  - Item 59: First Annual Boys' Fair and Handicraft Exhibit, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 60: Leadership Training, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 61: Salaried Employees' Retirement Income Indenture, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 62: A History and Analysis of this Company and its Recently-Acquired Foreign Affiliates, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 63: Reply Brief on Behalf of Chrysler Corporation Before Panel, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 64: Comments by Chrysler Corporation on Panel's report, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 65: Brief on Behalf of Chrysler Corporation Before Panel, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Item 66: Brief on Behalf of Chrysler Corporation, Publication (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Box 35, Folder (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Agreement Between the International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Agreement Between International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America and Local Unions 230, 889, 954, 1212, 1255, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Agreement Between International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America AND Local Union No. 412 and Chrysler Corporation, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Agreement Between International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America and Local Unions No. 7, 51, 227, 371, 685, 844, 961 and Chrysler Corporation, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Agreement Between International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America and Local Unions No. 7, 51, 227, 371, 490, 705 and Chrysler Corporation, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Agreement Between International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America and Local Unions No. 230, 899, 954 and Chrysler Corporation, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Agreement Between International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America and Local Unions No. 899, 954 and Chrysler Corporation, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation Automotive Body Division and the UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Agreement Entered into Between Chrysler Corporation for its Airtemp Division and the International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers Local 768-CIO, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Agreement Between Chrysler Division for its Airtemp Division and the Amalgamated Local No. 768, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Agreement between Chrysler Corporation and International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and the International Union UAW, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and the United Plant Guard Workers of America, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 22: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 23: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 24: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 25: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 26: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 27: Agreement Between International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America and Local No 7, 51, 227, 371, 685, 844, 961 and Chrysler Corporation, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 28: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 29: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 30: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 31: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW-CIO and Local Union No 212, 265, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 32: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 33: The Golden Age, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
    A Handbook for Engineering Division Retirants. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW-CIO and Local Union No. 212, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 35: Agreement Between International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America and Local Unions No. 230, 889, 594 and Chrysler Corporation, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 36: Basic Training Courses for Chrysler Supervisors, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 37: 25 Years of Steady Growth, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 38: Chrysler Corporation Department of Industrial Education, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 39: Your Chrysler Retirement Program, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 40: A Guide to Personnel Policies, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 41: The Story of an American Company, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 42: The Chrysler Corporation and You, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
    Some Things Employes Will Want to Know. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: What You Need to Know About Applying for Supplemental Unemployment Benefits, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 44: Your Guide to the Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 45: Greater Insurance Benefits For You, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 46: Your Insurance and Disability Benefits Program, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 47: Greater Insurance Benefits for You, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 48: Your Insurance Program, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 49: Your Insurance Program, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 50: Digest of Umpire Decisions, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 51: Performance Interview, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
    Suggestions for Counseling Subordinates on their Work. Item is in English.
  - Item 52: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and the UAW, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 53: What You Want to Know about Your Pension Plan, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 54: Highlights of your Pension Plan, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 55: Highlights of your Pension Plan, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 56: What you want to Know about Your Pension Plan, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 57: Highlights of Your Pension Plan, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 58: Highlights of our Pension Plan, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 59: Your Insurance Program, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 60: Your Insurance Program, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 61: The Obligation is Ours, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
    By L. L. Colbert. Item is in English.
  - Item 62: Your Guide to the Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 63: Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan Salaried and Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 64: Insurance Program Hourly Employees I.U.E, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 65: Insurance Program Hourly Employees U. A. W, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 66: Your Guide to the Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 67: Your Guide to the Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 68: What is your Opinion of te Job you Had with us?, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 69: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and the International Die Sinkers' Conference and the New Castle Die Sinkers' Lodge No. 120, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 70: Agreement Between Chrysler Corporation and the International Union of Operating Engineers Local 547, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 71: Chrysler Corporation's Purpose and Attitude is to Make Relations with Employees Better and Better, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 72: Chrysler- UAW Supplement, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 73: Corporate Personnel Procedure, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 74: Chrysler News, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Item 75: Chrysler Corporation Report to Shareholders, Publication (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Box 36, Folder (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Newspaper Contract Between Detroit News the Detroit Free Press, The Detroit Times Division of Hearst Publishing Co., Publication (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Agreement Between the Detroit Times Division of Hearst Publishing Company, Inc. and International Union of Operating Engineers Local No. 547, Publication (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Agreement Between Knight Newspapers, Inc. for and on Behalf of the Detroit Free Press Building and Internaional Union of Operating Engineers, Publication (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Agreement Between the Detroit News and International Union of Operating Engineers, Publication (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Contract Between Detroit News, the Detroit Free Press and the Detroit Times Division of Hearst Publishing Co., Inc. and Detroit Newspaper Printing Pressmen's Union No. 13, Publication (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Agreement Between Detroit Stereotypers' Union Number Nine and Detroit Publishers Association, he Detroit News The Detroit Times, The Detroit Free Press, Publication (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Supplementary Agreement Between the Detroit News, the Detroit Free Press and the Detroit Times Division of Hearst Publishing Co., Inc. and Detroit Paper Handlers' and Plate Handlers' Union No. 10, Publication (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Contract Between Detroit Newspaper Publishers Association and Detroit Mailers Union, Publication (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Records of Employees, Publication (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: The Romance of the Match, Publication (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: The Diamond Mach Company, Publication (Box 36, Folder 1)
    By Herbert Manchester. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Fifty Years of Match Making, Publication (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Handbook for Edison People, Publication (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Box 36, Folder (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Detroit Edison Today, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Report to Our Owners, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Open House Time, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: 800,000 More Kilowatts Coming up at Monroe Plant, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Our Company on the Move, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Special: Why we Must Have Higher Rates, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Christmas 1971 Publication, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Professional Manpower, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Disciplinary Procedure, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Employee Complaint Procedure, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Educational Assistance, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Safety Policy and Procedures, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Professional Opportunities for Engineering and Business Graduates, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Professional Opportunities for Enginering and business Graduates, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Detroit Edison Synchroscope, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Energy Crisis?, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Spray Welders Save us Money, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Detroit Edison Synchroscope, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: It's a Matter of Degrees!, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: Over 1 Billion for Nuclear Power, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: Supervisor News, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 22: Change in Company Policy on Auto Allowance Rates, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 23: Table of Organization, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 24: Agreement Between the Detroit Edison Co. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Box 36, Folder (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Planning for Supervisor Development, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Planning for Supervisor Development, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Sample Copies of the Material Distributed to Employees, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Idea Men reap Rewards and Save Money, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: A Task Force Approach to Control Room Planning, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Ludington Pumped Storage Power Plant, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: 1,000 Ways to Improve thru our Employee Proposal Plan, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Ideas Wiltoo, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: 1000 Ways to Improve, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: New First Aid Instructors: Learn how to Use Air Ambulance, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Sample Copies of Material Distributed to Employees on Business and Politics, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Man-Machine Communication, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By Lawrence Kanous. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Time Off - Applied Citizenship Activity, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Professional Opportunities for Graduates in a Leading Electric Light & Power System, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: Employee Citizenship Activities at the Detroit Edison Company, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: Some Human Factors in Safety, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: Sample Copies of Material Distributed to Employees on Economic Education, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 18: Guide to Management Development, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: Table of Organization, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 20: Fair Employment Practice Policy, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 21: Handbook for Edison People, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 22: The Fire Fighter and Electrical Equipment, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 23: Agreement Between Detroit Edison Company and Local Union No. 223 of the Utility Workers Union of America, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 24: Agreement Between Detroit Edison Company and Local Union No. 223, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 25: Agreement Between Detroit Edison Co. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 26: Education is a Good Investment, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 27: Agreement Between the Detroit Edison Co. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 28: Handbook for Edison People, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 29: Supervisor's Manual, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 30: Supervisors Manual, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 31: Cooperation or Attack, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Box 36, Folder (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Planning for Tomorrow, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Job Description, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Money Saving Ideas for Detroit Edison's Commercial Customers, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Wage-Utility Rates Compared, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Employee-Owned Automobiles Used on Company Business, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Electric Power and Social Policy, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Employee Stock Purchase Plan, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Alex Dow For 28 Years the President of "Detroit Edison", Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By LL D Brown. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Handbook for Edison People, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: ABC's of the Public Power Problem, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Planning for Tomorrow, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: I want to Know About the Electric Industry, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Your Job with Detroit Edison, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Your New Insurance Plans, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Detroit Edison Employee Clubs, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Outsourcing the New Group Life Insurance, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: Selection Test for Apprentice Lineman, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: For Cable Splicers Apprentices, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: Handbook for Edison People, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: Putting Your Ideas to Work, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: Agreement Between the Edison Co. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 22: Table of Organization, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 23: Table of Organization, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 24: Table of Organization, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 25: Pension, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 26: Weekly Inpection of Fire Protection Features, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 27: and More and More More, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 28: Training Buyers at Detroit Edison, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By D. F. Kigar. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: How Democratic can Industry Be?, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 30: Electric Power in the United States and Overseas, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Walker Cisler. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Electric Power Systems and Nuclear Power, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By Walker Ciser. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Management Inventory and Development in the Accounting Departments of the Detroit Edison Company, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By V.K Rowland. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Management Inventory and Development, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 34: Partners in Progress, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 35: Management Looks Ahead in the Electrical Industry, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 36: A Guide for the Selection of Supervisors, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 37: Supervisor Development Activities, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 38: Planning for Supervisor Development, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 39: Planning for Supervisor Development, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 40: Management Inventory and Development, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)